I look for you
I look for youEvery day, every night
I close my eyes
From the fear, from the light
As I wander down the avenue, so confused
Guess I'll try and force a smile
Pink lemonade sippin' on a Sunday
Couples holding hands on a runway
They're all posing in a picture frame
Whilst my world's crashing down
Solo shadow on a sidewalk
Just want somebody to die for
Sunshine livin' on a perfect day
While my world's crashing down
I just want somebody to die for
I long for you
Just a touch (does that scare you?)
Of your hand
You don't leave my mind
Lonely days, I'm feeling
Like a fool for dreaming
As I wander down the avenue,
so confused
Guess I'll try and force a smile
Pink lemonade sippin' on a Sunday
Couples holding hands on a runway
They're all posing in a picture frame
Whilst my world's crashing down
Solo shadow on a sidewalk
Just want somebody to die for
Sunshine livin' on a perfect day
While my world's crashing down
I just want somebody to die for
I just want somebody to die for (to die for)
Pink lemonade sippin' on a Sunday
Couples holding hands on a runway (oh)
They're all posing in a picture frame
Whilst my world's crashing down
Solo shadow on a sidewalk
Just want somebody to die for
Sunshine livin' on a perfect day
While my world's crashing down
I just want somebody to die for
I just want somebody to die for (to die for)