Excuse my French
But every time you turn your phone around
I'm just kind of lose my, lose my shit
Thinkin' it's another me, hangin' on the other line
I'm fine
I keep bringin' all my problems to a pillow fight
I'm just trying to get to you
But it's not your fault
No, it's not your fault
No, no
'Cause if I'm gonna learn how to love you
I need to unlearn how to love too
Need to unlearn how to run when it feels right
Oh my God, I'm tryin'
If I'm gonna learn how to choose you
I need to unlearn what I'm used to
Need to unlearn how to run when it feels right
Oh my God, I'm tryin'
Excuse my mouth
But every time you run a little late
Hanging with your friends, I
Freak the fuck out
Then you come home and your kiss tastes like wine
I'm fine
I keep bringing all my problems to a pillow fight
I'm just trying to get to you
But it's not your fault
No, it's not your fault
No, no
'Cause if I'm gonna learn how to love you
I need to unlearn how to love too
Need to unlearn how to run when it feels right
Oh my God, I'm tryin'
If I'm gonna learn how to choose you
I need to unlearn what I'm used to
Need to unlearn how to run when it feels right
Oh my God, I'm tryin'