Girl I've been all over the world
Looking for you
I'm known for taking what I think I deserve
And you're overdue
And if you listen you
can hear me through the radio
In that bright white noise
What I been missing in my life
What I been dreaming of
You'll be that girl
You'll be
Everything you want so let me get up there
I'm the baddest baby in the atmosphere
Tell me what you want so we can do just what you like
You make me feel that
La la la la la
Get a little closer to me girl
And you'll understand
'Cause if you want a guy that knows what you need
Well, then I'm your man
And if I listen I can hear you through my radio
In that bright white noise
What I been missing in my life
What I been dreaming of
You'll be that girl
You'll be
Everything you want so let me get up there
I'm the baddest baby in the atmosphere
Tell me what you want so we can do just what you like
You make me feel that
La la la la la