Tonight,
I want to give it all to you
In the darkness, there's so much
I want to do
And tonight, I want to lay it at your feet
'Cause girl, I was made for you
And girl, you were made for me
I was made for lovin' you, baby
You were made for lovin' me
And I can't get enough of you, baby
Can you get enough of me?
Tonight,
I want to see it in your eyes
Feel the magic,
there's something that drives me wild
And tonight,
we're gonna make it all come true
'
'Cause girl, you were made for me
And girl, I was made for you
I was made for lovin' you, baby
You were made for lovin' me
And I can't get enough of you, baby
Can you get enough of me?
I was made for lovin' you, baby
You were made for lovin' me
And I can give it all to you, baby
Can you give it all to me?
Oh, can't get enough
I can't get enough
I was made for lovin' you, baby
You were made for lovin' me
And I can't get enough of you, baby
Can you get enough of me?
I was made for lovin' you, baby
You were made for lovin' me
And I can't get enough of you, baby
Can you get enough of me?